http://www.timeanddate.com/information/privacy.html

Sign inHomeHome PageNewsletterAbout UsContact UsSite MapOur ArticlesAccount/SettingsWorld ClockMain World ClockExtended World ClockPersonal World ClockWorld Time Lookup UTC TimeTime ZonesTime Zones HomeTime Zone ConverterInternational Meeting PlannerEvent Time AnnouncerTime Zone MapTime Zone AbbreviationsDaylight Saving TimeTime Changes WorldwideTime DifferenceTime Zone NewsCalendarCalendars HomeCalendar 2020Calendar 2021Monthly CalendarPrintable Calendar (PDF)Add Your Own Calendar EventsCalendar CreatorAdvanced Calendar CreatorHolidays WorldwideOn This Day in HistoryMonths of the YearDays of the WeekAbout Leap YearsWeatherWorldwideLocal WeatherHour-by-Hour2-Week ForecastPast WeekClimateSun & MoonSun & Moon HomeSun CalculatorMoon CalculatorMoon PhasesNight SkyMeteor ShowersDay and Night MapMoon Light World MapEclipsesLive StreamsSeasonsTimersTimers HomeStopwatchTimerCountdown to Any DateChristmas CountdownNew Year CountdownCalculatorsCalculators HomeDate to Date Calculator (duration)Business Date to Date (exclude holidays)Date Calculator (add / subtract)Business Date (exclude holidays)Weekday CalculatorWeek Number CalculatorInternational Dialing CodesTravel Time CalculatorDistance CalculatorDistance SignpostApps & APIiOS AppsAndroid AppsWindows AppFree ClockFree CountdownAPI for DevelopersFree FunFree & Fun HomeFree Clock for Your SiteFree Countdown for Your SiteWord ClockFun HolidaysAlternative Age CalculatorDate Pattern CalculatorFun Fact ArticlesMy AccountMy AccountMy LocationMy UnitsMy EventsMy World ClockMy PrivacyPaid ServicesSign inRegister Home   Site information   Privacy StatementPrivacy StatementWe have a firm commitment to your privacy and data transparency at timeanddate.com.We value your privacy.This page discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for timeanddate.com. It also includes information regarding the processing of privacy information as stated in the new EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) of May 25, 2018.Lawful Basis for Processing Personal DataWe store some personal data in three cases:When consent is given by usersWhen processing is necessary for the purposes of our legitimate interests, such as the basic functionality of our site and servicesWhen processing is necessary for compliance with a legal obligation, such as storing payment records for our supporters and subscribersPersonal Data We ProcessAt timeanddate.com, we process some personal data. Below is a description of what, how, and why we gather and store user data.For all users who visit our website, we store:Web server log: IP address, pages visited by that IP address, link clicked to get here, browser name and version, and time stampThird parties collect similar information; see “Third-Party Privacy Policies” belowFor all users who actively make changes to site settings, we store:Setting preferences, which are not personally identifiable, i.e., the cookies are stored in the browser and not on our servers. These settings include: Calendar settingsPreferred units (temperature, distance, wind speed, etc.)Cities in your Personal World Clock“Home” locationFor users who sign in to their personal user account, we also store:Your email address (will not be sold nor distributed to any third party unrelated to timeanddate.com)Your password (hashed)Your chosen username, if anyList of log-ins (stored for up to 90 days)Log of changes you made to your account (stored for up to 90 days)Events added in PDF calendar listsFor newsletter subscribers, we store:Email address, IP address, and time of sign-upNewsletters received and openedAdditional parameters may be stored by MailChimp, who we use to send our newsletter; see “Third-Party Privacy Policies” belowFor paying supporters and subscribers, in addition to the above-mentioned data, we also store:Payment information: either the PayPal address or the last four digits of the credit card used for payment and a log of the steps taken to fulfill your order (stored for up to 90 days) Country of residence and, if submitted, street address, state, city, and ZIP/postal codeEmail address, if different than the one registered for the user accountWe use Braintree and Paypal for payments; see “Third-Party Privacy Policies” belowIP Address and CookiesWe use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers and to administer our websites. Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.Short-lived cookies die when you close the browser. Most long-lived cookies are stored for 10 years (1 year in the EU), to ensure your settings are not lost even if you visit the site infrequently, e.g., such as printing a calendar once a year. All cookies are stored in your browser, so your settings are lost when the cookies are deleted. You can avoid losing your settings by registering a free user account.When creating an account, you agree to our terms and conditions. Servers and Content DistributionOur servers are located in the USA, Germany, Singapore, Australia, and Norway. We also rely on third parties to host our services and our infrastructure, and to distribute our content, such as the newsletter.We take regular backups of our servers. Older backups are stored offline and are only used to recover data after a server crash or other incidents. Sensitive InformationWe have security measures in place. We will never ask for sensitive information. In the GDPR, “sensitive information” is defined as: “personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, and the processing of genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health or data concerning a natural person’s sex life or sexual orientation.” We recommend you do not add such information to our services, such as calendars, countdowns, or any other timeanddate.com application.External LinksThis site contains links to other sites. timeanddate.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of the linked websites.We use SurveyMonkey for online surveys. We may ask for your contact information, such as your email address. This information is used to contact you if necessary.AdvertisingWe use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit timeanddate.com. These companies may use aggregated information about your visits to this and other websites to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For more information about this practice and your possibility to opt out, click here.Third-Party Privacy PoliciesWe facilitate logging in and sharing via social media accountsWe use Braintree and Paypal for supporters and subscribersWe use MailChimp to distribute our NewsletterThird-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website and/or other websitesGoogle's use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and/or other websitesUsers may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting YourAdChoices or our privacy settings pageThird parties we use for advertising:Index Exchange ExponentialSubject to your consent, Exponential Interactive, Inc collects and profile personal data in the form of IP address and cookie ID from users on our website to provide targeted online advertising and ad measurement. You may change your consent decision at any time. For more details including access requests and complaints, review their privacy policy or contact their data protection officer via privacy@exponential.comExponential uses ANON_ID (persistent tracking cookie), by domain tribalfusion.com. The anonymous hashed id in the cookie links the web user's browser to a profile which contains the behaviours the user has displayed. This is stored for 3 months. Google DFP/AdX Google Admob OpenXApp Nexus Rubicon ProjectConversant Sovrn CriteoSonobi RhythmOneDistrict-M bRealTime MicrosoftThird parties we use for logging in:Facebook Google MicrosoftLinkedIn Amazon Right to Receive InformationAs of May 25, 2018, the new EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) provides every user the right to receive a copy of the information we have stored about them. You may download a copy of your personal data on our privacy settings page.Deleting Stored DataUsers have the right to have personal information deleted upon request. You can delete your user account via the button at the bottom of your account page.If you have sent us emails, and you want to delete them, please send an email to webmaster@timeanddate.com.Contacting the WebsiteIf you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this website, or your dealings with this website, please contact:Time and Date ASKanalsletta 4NO-4033 StavangerNorwaywebmaster@timeanddate.com Become a Supporter Help us keep up the good work. timeanddate.com
About Us
Our history
Contact Us
Feedback
Privacy Statement
Terms & Conditions
Refunds & Cancellations
Copyright
